traderxp.com 2012-10-17

# TraderXp - Privacy Policy - TraderXP

  * home
  * privacy policy

PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY   

TraderXP does its utmost to ensure the privacy, confidentiality and security of its clients are preserved both throughout their interaction with the company and afterwards, to the fullest extent achievable by the company.

1. When clients register with TraderXP they acknowledge their willingness to share with the company certain private information which we use for the purpose of confirming the client’s identity and ensuring the security of their deposits and trading account. This information is collected in line with our stringent verification procedures which are used to deter international money laundering operations and to ensure the security and safety of our customer’s trading activity throughout.

2. Our clients undertake to supply us with true, updated and accurate information about their identity. Furthermore  they are required to state categorically that they are registering and trading on their own behalf and are not seeking at any time to act any manner which could be considered fraudulent nor are they seeking to impersonate any other individuals for any purposes whatsoever.

3. TraderXP’s data collection procedures include the collection of client’s freely disclosed information as shared with the company, in addition to the placement of cookies for the purposes of gathering data about the manner in which client’s interact with the TraderXP website. These tools for gathering client’s information are employed for the purpose of ensuring the customer’s own security and all data collected by the company is shared only with individuals within the company who are involved with the verification of customer account information for the express purpose of ensuring the customer’s confidentiality and security.  

4. TraderXP will never disclose any private or otherwise confidential information in regards to our clients and former clients to third parties without the express, written consent of our clients, except in such specific cases in which disclosure is a requirement under law, or is otherwise necessary in order to perform verification analysis on the client’s identity for the purposes of safeguarding their account and securing their personal information. 

5. By registering with TraderXP and through the voluntary interaction they undertake with TraderXP’s products and services the client confirms and agrees that they consent to the use of all or part of the information they supply concerning their TraderXP trading account, the transactions they undertake through it and the interactions which they perform with the company on behalf of the company. All interactions the customer undertakes with the cmpanywill be stored by the company for the purposes of record and as such may be employed by the company in such cases that disputes arise between clients and TraderXP.

6. TraderXP does its utmost to ensure the confidentiality of its clients personal information including the implementation of data protection procedures designed to ensure client confidentiality. TraderXP ensures that its data protection policy is regularly updated in order to ensure that client’s confidential information is continually safeguarded.

7. From time to time TraderXP may contact clients whether by phone or email for the purpose of offering them further information about TraderXP, binary options trading or financial market trading. In addition the company may, on occasion, seek to contact clients, whether by phone or by email, for the purpose of informing them of unique promotional offerings provided by TraderXP for the client. Clients consent to the receipt of such contact when they consent to our terms and conditions of use when registering with TraderXP. Any person wishing to opt out of further contact with TraderXP at anytime whatsoever is entitled to do so, simply by contacting the company whether by phone or email and requesting that no further contact on behalf of the company be made.  

How to Trade 

  * Binary Options
  * One Touch
  * 

  * 1)

Choose from our wide variety of assets.  

  * 2)

Simply press the “CALL” button if you believe that the value will exceed the listed price at expiration, or press the “PUT” button if you feel that the value will decline below the listed price at expiration.  

  * 3)

Insert your initial investment sum and press the "Apply" button.  

  * 4)

Gain up to 75% of your investment.

What goes down, must come up.  A decade of tax cuts is coming to an end in 2010 and... 

Jim Cramer says Europe's central bank is dropping the ball. Here's his take. 

Global stock markets are regularly seeing three-percent swings as investors grapple... 

Don't lose sleep over the market turmoil! Oppenheimer's Carter Worth thinks the stock... 

The debt crisis is a game changer for the market and Europe is now at risk of heading... 

XL Capital has been facing a negative trend recently, and yesterday the bears turned it... 

Plus, will the Treasury indiscriminately sell its Citi stake, killing the share price?... 

In the investment strategist world, I tend to be pretty cautious. I do believe that... 

Stock pared their earlier losses Monday, but investors are continuing to worry about... 

The new SEC rules on the single stock circuit breakers were published today in the... 

Stocks wobbled in mid-afternoon trading Monday following a short-lived rally. How... 

Action in three key areas of the market suggest the recent sell-off might not be such a... 

With one major banking crisis behind us, Monument Securities Chief Economist Stephen... 

The year-long uptrend in the stock market is over and commodities are also set to... 

Stocks are likely to continue their aggressive decline and shed another 20 percent as... 

As far as we’ve fallen, Cramer says, we haven’t dropped enough. He explains what it... 

Nearly every large-cap U.S. company has some form of exposure to Europe and some are... 

Investors can realize strong returns on municipal bonds and federally-instituted Build... 

Markets are significantly undervalued in terms of corporate earnings, and stocks are... 

Interesting article on Bloomberg yesterday (Wednesday) regarding the drubbing investors...
